updown.com 2015-04-25

# Stock Market Game - Practice investing $1,000,000 - UpDown.com

The UpDown respects your right to privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out and explains our privacy policy Please read the following to understand our practices regarding personal information and how they affect you as a user of TheUpDown.com. This statement discloses our current privacy practices; if we make material changes to these practices, we will announce them. If you have questions concerning your privacy at The UpDown, please email us at contact@updown.com and we will promptly respond. 

## Which information do we collect about our users?

TheUpDown collects information from different parts of our web site so that we can provide a more interesting and useful service, as well as more appropriate advertising. We ask for personal information including (but not limited to) your name, email address, and other personal information when you register to our Web site, or if you sign up for special or personalized services such as contests, surveys and promotions. The more information you provide, the better we are able to customize our service to you. However, unless we get your approval, we will not display your name and address. 

If you use our "Email page to a friend" service, you will need to provide us with your friend's name and email address and your email address as a return address. We will automatically send this person a one-time email as well as an invitation to visit and register with our site. We will not use these email addresses for any other purpose. 

## How do we use the information?

Our objective in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most personalized experience possible, and to provide our advertisers with an efficient way to reach the right audience. 

In addition to the use of personal information to operate the site, The UpDown also gathers anonymous information, which may be used by The UpDown or shared with its partners. This information does not personally identify you, but may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "cookies" "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. 

We conduct research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based upon the information you provide us when you register or participate in contests or other promotions on our site, or based upon the information on our server log files. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. We may also notify you of products, services, or areas of our site that we think may interest you based on the information we've received. If you would prefer us not to contact you for these purposes, simply go to our opt-out page and let us know. 

When we show rankings of our members and their portfolios, we will use your unique member login name as a screen name. Please ensure that all information included in login names is acceptable to you for public display. 

Sometimes we ask for personal information when providing special features and services. You do not have to give us that information, but without it, you may not be able to take advantage of those products or services. For example, you will be unable to track your personal stock portfolio on our site unless you input the stocks you own, and you may not be able to gain access to certain areas of our site unless you register and/or subscribe. 

## Do we disclose any of the personal information?

The UpDown will not disclose any personally identifiable information about individual users, except as described in this Privacy Statement. With the few exceptions that we explain here, we do not give, rent, lend, or sell individual information to our advertisers, although we do provide aggregate information. We may also use this aggregated information to help the advertisers reach the kind of audience they want. We may also disclose aggregate information in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

## What measures to we take to protect your information?

The UpDown is committed to protecting your personal information. We store information you provide us on our secure servers. Personalized areas of our sites, such as My UpDown, are password-protected. Only you have access to these password-protected areas. Do not share your passwords with anyone. The UpDown will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. If you are using a computer to which others have access, such as one in a computer lab, Internet cafe, or public library, always remember to log out and close your browser window when leaving our site. 

## How can you correct or revise information that we have about you?

If you want to correct or change information in your Personal Profile, you can do so in the My UpDown section. 

## How do we protect children's privacy?

Our sites are not directed at children under the age of 13. We operate our sites in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 13. 

## Does The UpDown use IP addresses and cookies?

### IP Addresses

Your Web browser or email application automatically provides your Internet Protocol address ("IP address") to other computers with which you communicate over the Internet, so that they know where to send you information. 

We receive an IP address each time you view one of our Web pages, because the browser automatically reports it to us. We also may store the IP address when you register with The UpDown. 

We may use IP addresses for various purposes, including: 

  * Diagnosing service or technology problems. 
  * Assessing and maintaining system security. 
  * Displaying the most appropriate advertising or content. 
  * Studying how people use our site and how we can improve it. 
  * Reporting to advertisers about aggregate, but not individual, information derived from IP addresses. 

### Cookies

Cookies are used on our sites in the following ways:

  * We use cookies to access your stored account information automatically when you log on to our site, in order to deliver a better and more personalized service. 
  * We use cookies to estimate our audience size and usage patterns. The unique cookie that is given to each browser accessing The UpDown is then used to determine usage patterns and help us target content and ads based upon user interests. 
  * We use cookies to allow you to access your account information automatically, as well as make changes to your personal information. 
  * Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can configure yours to refuse cookies or notify you when you've received one. Browsers differ, so check your "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you reject cookies on our sites, though, you will not be able to access all areas of them or use many of their features. When you accept our cookies, we cannot use them to find out who you really are, unless you tell us. 

For more information about cookies, read the unofficial Cookie FAQ from [CookieCentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/ "cookiecentral.com").
